when we are busy whining, we might not call it whining because we're like, no, like I'm calling
out the things that are a problem. Like I'm saying the things that are in the way. I'm just like
frustrated that they're not what they are. And I can, y'all, y'all know that I know about that.
Okay. But then there's also like, okay, once you've established that, now what? At a certain
point, you have to give space to actually let the inspiration come to you or let the knowledge or
let the flow come to you. And the whining and the complaining, it becomes force at a certain
point because you're literally forcing yourself to just be stuck in like, I don't like this.
And that's when we can also go into like the abundance versus the scarcity mindset, because
the abundance mindset will say, well, you don't like this, but like, what do you like? And like,
how can we like center that versus what you don't like? This life thing ain't easy, y'all. Trust me.
We all trying to figure it out. We all trying to flow, not force it out.
Yeah.